RG 161:001, Connecticut State Police
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. State Police Investigation Files, 1919-1998; 293.75 cubic feet
  - State Leasing case, 1970-1978; 1987-018; 29.25 cubic feet
    - Stuart Smith, tape no. 11-A, 1977 August 9 (Box 12)
    - Stuart Smith, tape no. 11-B, 1978 April 20 (Box 12)
    - Adolph Carlson, tape no. 12-A, 1977 May 27 (Box 12)
    - Adolph Carlson, tape no. 12-B, 1977 July 21 (Box 12)
    - Chester Zaniewski, tape no. 13-A, 1978 April 3 (Box 12)
    - Chester Zaniewski, tape no. 13-B, 1978 April 10 (Box 12)
    - Daniel McKinnon, tape no. 14-A & B, 1978 June 20 (Box 12)
    - What's Happening, tape no. 15, 1974 March 16 (Box 12)
    - What's Happening, tape no. 16, 1973 August 10 (Box 12)
    - Henry Margolis, tape no. 17-A & B, 1976 February 26 (Box 12)
    - Henry Margolis, tape no. 17-C, undated (Box 12)
    - Henry Margolis, tape no. 17-D & E, 1976 February 4 (Box 12)
    - Rodger Ladd, tape no. 18-A, 1977 November 14 (Box 12)
    - Rodger Ladd, tape no. 18-B, C, D, 1977 November 18 (Box 12)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 13)
    - Rodger Ladd, tape no. 18-E & F, 1977 November 18 (Box 13)
    - Bradley Biggs, tape no. 19-A & B, 1975 December 10 (Box 13)
    - Bradley Biggs, tape no. 19-C, 1976 May 3 (Box 13)
    - Robert Demchack, tape no. 20-A, B, C, 1976 June 23 (Box 13)
    - Gene DeMatteo, tape no. 21-A, B, C, 1976 June 15 (Box 13)
    - Chet Zaniewski, tape no. 22-1 to 22-D, 1976 January 28 (Box 13)
    - George Pawcikowski, tape no. 23-A, 1976 July 28 (Box 13)
    - George Pawcikowski, tape no. 23-B, 1976 July 28 (Box 14)
    - DEP Commissioner, James Bergen, tape 24-A & B, 1976 April 23 (Box 14)
    - E. Koslowski, tape no. 25-A & B, 1976 January 14 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous papers (Box 14)
    - Leasing Investigation-Sherwill file (Box 14)
    - State Leasing Investigation (Box 14)
    - Review of Allan Schaefer tapes (Box 14)
    - Affidavit of Harry Gambel (Box 14)
    - Phoenix Building file (Box 15)
    - CSP Chronology (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Art Banks (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Robert Bokelman (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Charles Searle (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Henry Fagan (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Brian Gaffney (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Gerald McCann (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Thomas Montgomery (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of William Shure (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Herbert Smith (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of James Stewart (Box 15)
    - Affidavit of Art Banks (Box 15)
    - GHCC Board resolutions (Box 15)
    - Brokers and $50,000.00 note, copy (Box 15)
    - CSP Reports (Box 15)
    - DeLorenzo for Mayor checking account (Box 15)
    - CSP Report, Y-75-205 (Box 15)
    - CSP Reports (Box 16)
    - CSP Reports - Winsted (Box 16)
    - Riverview Realty file (Box 17)
    - Riverview Realty CSP report, Y-75-0218C (Box 17)
    - CSP Report - MVD and DOT sites in Winsted (Box 17)
    - Winsted Leasing Case Overview (Box 17)
    - Documents relating to Winsted property (Box 17)
    - Leasing investigation (Box 18)
    - CSP Reports, C.O. 389 and 513 (Box 18)
    - CSP Reports, Y-76-0114-C (Box 18)
    - UCONN Medical Center file (Box 18)
    - UCONN Cases referred by R. Feingold (Box 18)
    - Report - BX Cable (Box 18)
    - Report - Grass seeding, CO 417 (Box 18)
    - Report - C.O. 448 (Box 18)
    - Report - C.O. 380 (Box 18)
    - Report - C.O. 473 (Box 18)
    - Medical Center Fire Alarms, CO 461 (Box 19)
    - Overpass (Box 19)
    - Manaford patio (Box 19)
    - Medical Center masonry wall, CO 448 (Box 19)
    - Wage/Salary records (Box 19)
    - Medical Center/BX Cable file (Box 19)
    - Westinghouse CO (Box 20)
    - Medical Center (photographs) (Box 20)
    - Medical Center, CO 465 Terminal Strips (Box 20)
    - Medical Center, CO 389 Westinghouse Hardware (Box 20)
    - Westinghouse file (Box 20)
    - PWD technical manual (Box 20)
    - CSP Report, Y-78-0053-C (Box 20)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0205-C (Box 20)
    - Transcript of Jay Jackson (Box 20)
    - Transcript of Allan Schaefer (Box 21)
    - Additional papers, HE-2 (Box 21)
    - CSP Report Larceny, Y-77-0251-C (Box 21)
    - CSP Report Larceny, Y-75-0205-C (Box 21)
    - CSP Report Eastern Connecticut Dial System, Y-76-0153-C (Box 21)
    - State's Attorney - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - FBI - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - CSP Report Bribery, Y-75-0229-C (Box 22)
    - CSP Report Verbal Threat, Y-76-0009-C (Box 22)
    - CSP Report Waterford Lease, Y-77-0096-C (Box 22)
    - Licamele Lease (Box 22)
    - CSP Report Larceny SCCC, Y-76-0021-C (Box 23)
    - CSP Report Larceny GHCC, Y-76-0041-C (Box 23)
    - CSP Report GHCC lease, Y-76-0011-C (Box 23)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 23)
    - Original documents HE-2 (Box 23)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 23)
    - Harry Gambel, tape no. 1-A, 1977 May 27 (Box 23)
    - Harry Gambel, tape no. 1-B, 1977 August 4 (Box 23)
    - Harry Gambel, tape no. 1-C & D, 1977 August 10 (Box 23)
    - Harry Gambel, tape no. 1-E, 1977 September 26 (Box 23)
    - Harry Gambel, tape no. 1-F, 1977 August 10 (Box 23)
    - Harry Gambel, tape no. 1-G, 1977 November 14 (Box 23)
    - Larry Stern, tape no. 2-A, 1977 June 10 (Box 23)
    - Larry Stern, tape no. 2-B, 1977 June 15 (Box 23)
    - Larry Stern, tape no. 2-C & D, 1977 June 23 (Box 23)
    - Re-tape of Norelco tapes, tape no. 3-1 (Box 23)
    - Brian Gafney, tape no. 4-A & B, 1978 April 7 (Box 24)
    - Theodore DeLorenzo, tape no. 5-A, 1977 September 15 (Box 24)
    - Theodore DeLorenzo, tape no. 5-B, 1977 September 29 (Box 24)
    - Bernard Mussman, tape no. 6-A, 1977 June 15 (Box 24)
    - Bernard Mussman, tape no. 6-B, 1977 October 6 (Box 24)
    - Jerry McCann, tape no. 7-A & B, 1978 April 3 (Box 24)
    - Jerry McCann, tape no. 7-C & D, 1977 May 26 (Box 24)
    - Jerry McCann, tape no. 7-E, 1977 June 1 (Box 24)
    - Jerry McCann, tape no. 7-F, 1977 June 7 (Box 24)
    - Robert Weinerman, tape no. 8-A, B, C, 1978 April 12 (Box 24)
    - Art Banks, tape no. 9-A, 1977 May 20 (Box 24)
    - Art Banks, tape no. 9-B, 1977 June 14 (Box 25)
    - Art Banks, tape no. 9-C, 1977 September 13 (Box 25)
    - Allan Schaefer, tape no. 10-A, 1977 October 5 (Box 25)
    - Allan Schaefer, tape no. 10-B, C, D, 1977 October 19 (Box 25)
    - Allan Schaefer, tape no. 10-E, 1977 November 17 (Box 25)
    - John Marsella, tape no. 26-A & B, 1975 December 15 (Box 25)
    - Henry Margolis, tape no. 27-A & B, 1976 March 18 (Box 25)
    - Homicki, tape no. 28-A & B, 1976 September 24 (Box 25)
    - James Bergen, tape no. 29-A & B, 1978 August 22 (Box 25)
    - Edward Roscoe, tape no. 30-A, 1978 August 3 (Box 25)
    - Edward Roscoe, tape no. 30-B, 1978 August 22 (Box 26)
    - W. Chambrullo, tape no. 31, 1976 December 1 (Box 26)
    - Freedman, tape no. 32, 1976 November 30 (Box 26)
    - W. Powanda, tape no. 33, 1975 December 12 (Box 26)
    - N. Vicczgo, tape no. 34, 1976 August 17 (Box 26)
    - M. Sussman, tape no. 35, 1977 September 26 (Box 26)
    - H. Armstrong, tape no. 36, 1977 September 17 (Box 26)
    - R. Joins, tape no. 37, 1977 July 14 (Box 26)
    - A. Petrella, tape no. 38, 1976 August 17 (Box 26)
    - W. Robinson, tape no. 39, 1975 January 8 (Box 26)
    - Berdick, tape no. 40-A & B, 1976 April 14 (Box 26)
    - Berdick, tape no. 40-C, 1976 August 17 (Box 26)
    - A. Banks, tape no. 41-A & B, 1976 March 16 (Box 26)
    - Donald Kerr, tape no. 42, 1975 December 16 (Box 26)
    - Neckerman, tape no. 43, 1976 September 30 (Box 27)
    - Kessler, tape no. 44, 1976 May 14 (Box 27)
    - Gilbert, tape no. 45, 1975 December 9 (Box 27)
    - T. O'Marra, tape no. 46, 1976 January 22 (Box 27)
    - A. Abeshouse, tape no. 47, 1975 December 5 (Box 27)
    - Newton, tape no. 48, 1975 November 25 (Box 27)
    - Roscoe Barone, tape no. 49, 1975 November 26 (Box 27)
    - Stanley Page, tape no. 50, 1978 September 19 (Box 27)
    - R. Demchack, tape no. 51-A, 1976 July 7 (Box 27)
    - R. Demchack, tape no. 51-B, 1976 October 13 (Box 27)
    - S. Freedman, tape no. 52, 1976 November 30 (Box 27)
    - R. Hinze, tape no. 53, 1975 December 1 (Box 27)
    - M. Chambrullo, tape no. 54-A, 1976 December 1 (Box 27)
    - M. Chambrullo, tape no. 54-B, 1976 December 15 (Box 27)
    - Leasing investigation Riverview Realty (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous leasing - Winsted (Box 28)
    - Original copy of Review Realty report, Y-75-0218-C (Box 28)
    - Land records (Box 28)
    - CSP Reports re: Winsted (Box 29)
    - Documents re: Winsted property (Box 29)
    - Drafts - Riverview Report (Box 29)
    - Norwalk Community College (Box 29)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, Larceny GHCC, Y-76-0041-C (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, Verbal Threat, Y-76-009-C (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, Bribery, Y-75-0229-C (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, Larceny SCCC, Y-76-0021-C (Box 29)
    - Licamele Lease (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, GHCC lease, Y-76-0011-C (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, Y-77-0096-C (Box 29)
    - Winsted - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
    - CSP Report, Eastern CT Dial System, Y-76-0153-C (Box 30)
    - CSP Report, Larceny - Winchester, Y-77-0251-C (Box 30)
    - American Bar Association Report, 1976 November 9 (Box 30)
    - Documents for GHCC (Box 30)
    - Leasing investigation by Sherwill (Box 31)
    - GHCC Audit work papers (Box 31)
    - Barone letter to Zaniewski (Box 31)
    - Hurwitz letter to Community PWD, 1977 September 28 (Box 31)
    - Bauer letter to Schaefer, 1977 January 20 (Box 31)
    - Quarrier letter to Rockwell, 1977 August 3 (Box 31)
    - G. Gunther letter of complaint (Box 31)
    - Gionfriddo letter to Zaniewski (Box 31)
    - Brunette letter to Zaniewski (Box 31)
    - LaPorte letter to Zaniewski (Box 31)
    - Barone letter to Baldwin (Box 31)
    - Zaniewski letter to Brunette (Box 31)
    - Attorney Roscoe file (Box 31)
    - Jackson memoranda to Weinerman (Box 31)
    - Barone letter to Feldman (Box 31)
    - Brunette letter to McKinnon (Box 31)
    - Weinerman letter to Schaefer (Box 31)
    - Request for purchase proposals (Box 31)
    - Rough draft history of 1 Myrtle Street (Box 31)
    - Brunette letter to McKinnon (Box 31)
    - Information itemized for Review Board (Box 31)
    - Attorney Roscoe file (Box 31)
    - Rockwell's correspondence, 59 folders (Box 32)
    - Union Commerce Bank file (Box 32)
    - Bond for Deed (Box 32)
    - Resolution of CFU Management Corp. (Box 32)
    - Sloate Square brochure (Box 32)
    - Rockwell's letter to Roscoe (Box 32)
    - Weinerman letter to Jackson (Box 32)
    - McTeauges correspondence (Box 32)
    - Allan Schaefer correspondence (Box 32)
    - Rough draft, August 25 (Box 32)
    - Capitol Center Property Acquisition for State Agency Needs report (Box 32)
    - Attorney Roscoe file (Box 32)
    - CSP Report, Y-78-0053-C (Box 32)
    - Affidavit of Allan Schaefer (Box 32)
    - CFU Management Corp (Box 32)
    - Real Estate Certification (Box 32)
    - Affidavit of Weinerman (Box 32)
    - Chet Zaniewski correspondence (Box 32)
    - PWD outline and conclusion on 1 Myrtle Street (Box 32)
    - Real Estate listings (Box 32)
    - Lease proposal outline (Box 32)
    - Bond for Deed $3,485,000.00 (Box 32)
    - Bond for deed $3,570,000.00 (Box 32)
    - PWD for 1 Myrtle Street (Box 32)
    - Affidavits and documents given to State's attorney (Box 33)
    - Appraisal - Dow and Condom (Box 33)
    - Appraisal - Richard Barry (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 33)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 33)
    - Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Affidavit of Zaniewski (Box 33)
    - Cavanna's statements (Box 33)
    - CBT to Zaniewski (Box 33)
    - Option Agreement (Box 33)
    - CSP reports (Box 33)
    - Report Special Investigation of John Williams (Box 33)
    - Affidavit of Dino Nucci (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous re: F.M. Airlines (Box 34)
    - Transcript of Allan Schaefer (Box 35)
    - Zaniewski comments to Sub-Committee on Leasing (Box 35)
    - Specifications of DOT Garage, Waterford, CT (Box 35)
    - CSP Report, Y-78-0053-C (Box 35)
    - CSP Report, Norwich Labor Dept, Y-76-0142-C (Box 35)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 36)
    - B. Bayus, 1976 April 8 (Box 36)
    - E. Koslowski, 1976 January 14 (Box 36)
    - R. Gilbert, 1976 December 9 (Box 36)
    - A. Petrella, 1976 August 17 (Box 36)
    - W. Powanda, 1975 December 12 (Box 36)
    - R. Weinerman, 1978 April 12 (Box 36)
    - R. DeLorenzo, 1977 September 29 (Box 36)
    - W. Robinson, 1975 January 8 (Box 36)
    - R. Demchack, 1976 June 23, July 7 (Box 36)
    - R. Mussman, 1977 June 15, October 6 (Box 36)
    - N. Vicczgo, 1976 August 17 (Box 37)
    - L. Stern, 1977 June 10, 23 (Box 37)
    - E. Roscoe, 1978 August 2 (Box 37)
    - G. Pawlikowski, 1976 July 28 (Box 37)
    - K. Babcock, 1976 April 8 (Box 37)
    - C. Zaniewski, 1978 April 10 (Box 37)
    - A. Carlson, 1977 July 21, August 2 (Box 37)
    - A. Schaefer, 1977 October 5, November 17 (Box 38)
    - H. Gampel, 1977 May 27, August 10, September 26 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous tapes (Box 38)
    - Bodhad Bayus (Box 38)
    - Kenneth Babcock (Box 38)
    - Gene DeMatteo, 1976 June 15 (Box 39)
    - Art Banks, 1977 May 20, June 14, September 13 (Box 39)
    - Jerry McCann, 1977 April 3, May 26, June 1 (Box 39)
    - J. Bergell, 1978 August 22 (Box 39)
    - R. Demchack, 1976 June 23 (Box 39)
    - D. Burdick, 1976 August 17 (Box 39)
    - G. Pawlikowski, 1976 July 28 (Box 40)
    - M. Chambrullo, 1976 December 15 (Box 40)
    - S. Freedman, 1976 November 10 (Box 40)
    - M. Chambrullo, 1976 December 1 (Box 40)
    - D. McKinnon, 1976 June 20 (Box 40)
    - Jay Jackson, 1978 October 19 (Box 40)
    - What's Happening (Box 40)
    - Wolcott #166 (Box 40)
    - Proposal - Central Naugatuck Valley Higher Ed, Waterbury (Box 40)
    - Construction site photographs, Y-75-205-C (Box 40)
    - Public Works Technical Manual (Box 41)
    - Site development in Waterbury, HE-2 (Box 41)
    - CSP Reports, Y-75-205-C (Box 41)
    - MBI Cash receipts (Box 42)
    - Manaford Brothers Inc. - disbursement extension records (Box 42)
    - Manaford receipts and disbursements (Box 42)
    - MBI disbursements and extensions (Box 42)
    - Structural Fill Case, Waterbury HE-2 (Box 43)
    - B. Sherwill (Box 43)
    - Affidavit of D. Burdick (Box 43)
    - Affidavit of D. Nucci (Box 43)
    - Structural Gravel materials HE-2 (Box 43)
    - Y-76-008-C, HE-2 (Box 43)
    - CSP Reports, Y-76-008-C, HE-2 (Box 44)
    - UCONN case re: Feingold (Box 44)
    - UCONN Medical Center - BX Cable reports (Box 44)
    - Interdepartmental messages from Feingold to Weinerman (Box 44)
    - Medical Center masonry wall, CO 448 (Box 45)
    - Grass seeding, CO 417 (Box 45)
    - Medical Center Fire Alarms, CO 461 (Box 45)
    - Manaford patio (Box 45)
    - Reports, stones in topsoil, CO 380 (Box 45)
    - Reports, terminal block wiring, CO 465 (Box 45)
    - Reports, repair sod, CO 473 (Box 45)
    - Reports, Westinghouse Hardware, CO 380 and 513 (Box 46)
    - Freedman-Nager Electric, payroll ledger (Box 46)
    - Westinghouse contract order (Box 46)
    - CSP Reports, Y-75-0205-C, 1978 (Box 46)
    - CSP Reports, Y-76-0063-C (Box 46)
    - DOT 160 Pascone Place, Newington (Box 46)
    - CSP Reports, Y-76-0063-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Reports, Attempted Bribery, Y-75-0227-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Eastern CT State College Dial Retrieval System (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0114-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-009-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-77-0091-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0148-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0153-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0142-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-77-0251-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0011-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-008-C (Box 47)
    - CSP Report, Y-76-0264-C (Box 47)
    - Hot sheet, 1970-1975 (Box 48)
    - Y-76-009-C tapes (Box 48)
    - Chronology of HE-2 (Box 48)
    - Miscellaneous contracts HE-2 (Box 48)
    - C.M. contracts, HE-2 (Box 48)
    - Final Reports Legislative Committee (Box 48)
    - Weighted Unit Prices (Box 48)
    - DeMatteo - Reports (Box 48)
    - New Haven Testing Labs (Box 48)
    - Olson and Miller documents (Box 48)
    - Biggs International Development Corp. (Box 48)
    - Manaford (Box 48)
    - Stein, Sapeck and Ames (Box 48)
    - CSP Report, T. Deleo (Box 48)
    - HE-2 Federal Funds (Box 48)
    - Materials received from DeMatteo (Box 48)
    - Henry Margolis (Box 49)
    - DeMatteo Construction (Box 49)
    - Material on charge order reports (Box 49)
    - Review folder (Box 49)
    - Manaford and MBI loan and exchange records (Box 49)
    - Affidavit of Henry Margolis (Box 49)
    - Mattatuck College, HE-2 documents (Box 49)
    - Construction MGR analysis (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 49)
    - Henry Margolis file (Box 49)
    - Architect's drawing of HE Center, Waterbury (Box 49)
    - Initial Report, Y-76-0114-C (Box 49)
    - CSP Report, Riverview Realty (Box 50)
    - Case reports, CO 380 (Box 50)
    - Reports, UCONN fire alarms, CO 461 (Box 50)
    - Change order, UCONN masonry wall, CO 448 (Box 50)
    - CSP Reports, UCONN Westinghouse, CO 513 (Box 50)
    - Original statements of UCONN Medical Center (Box 50)
    - BX Cable UCONN, Y-77-0091-C (Box 50)
    - Report UCONN, CO 473 (Box 50)
    - Report UCONN, CO 417 (Box 50)
    - Report UCONN, CO 465 (Box 50)
    - Report Easter Connecticut State College (Box 50)
    - CSP Reports, Y-76-0114-C (Box 50)
    - Attorney General correspondence (Box 50)
    - Winsted Leases, Riverview Realty (Box 50)
    - Violation of corrupt practices (Box 50)
    - Middlesex College (Box 50)
    - MANNIX Report on leasing (Box 50)
    - General Assembly, Joint Committee on Appropriations (Box 50)
    - Lieberman Committee Leasing Report (Box 51)
    - American Bar Association Report, 1975 March 3 (Box 51)
    - Riverview Realty leases in Winsted documents (Box 51)
    - MANNIX report (Box 51)
    - Appendix of Sub-committee report, 1975 February 15 (Box 51)
    - CSP Reports, Y-76-0063-C (Box 51)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 51)
    - CSP Reports, Middlesex College, Y-75-002180-C (Box 51)
    - CSP Reports, O'Marra, Y-74-0006-C (Box 51)
    - State Police report on Leasing Probe, 1975 (Box 51)
    - Newspaper clippings, GHCC (Box 51)
    - Phoenix chart (Box 52)
    - Checking account of T. DeLorenzo for Mayor (Box 52)
    - Building permits issued to Schaefer, 1974 (Box 52)
    - Financial statement, DeLorenzo for Mayor campaign (Box 52)
    - Copy of $50,000.00 note signed by DeLorenzo (Box 52)
    - Work sheet for analysis of DeLorenzo for Mayor campaign (Box 52)
    - Complete file of GHCC (Box 52)
    - Affidavits in the Phoenix case, 14 folders (Box 53)
    - Review of Schaefer tapes (Box 53)
    - Affidavit of Harry Gamper (Box 53)
    - Affidavit of S. Smith (Box 53)
    - Stanley Page correspondence to Governor (Box 53)
    - Roger Leuba file (Box 53)
    - Affidavit of Harry Gampel, 1977 September (Box 53)
    - Adolph Carlson file (Box 53)
    - FBI letter requesting Meskill investigation file (Box 53)
    - Bernie Mussman file (Box 53)
    - Travelers (Box 53)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 53)
    - T. Montgomery file (Box 53)
    - Affidavit of Art Banks (Box 53)
    - Possess property reports and receipts turned over to FBI (Box 53)
    - Affidavit of B. Gaffney (Box 53)
    - Y-76-0041-C file (Box 53)
    - Governor Meskill testimony in Washington (Box 53)
    - GHCC notes from legislative file (Box 54)
    - Building permits for Phoenix building renovations (Box 54)
    - GHCC file on Governor Meskill (Box 54)
    - Larry Stern file (Box 54)
    - Davis and Nye purchase orders (Box 54)
    - MXCC Equipment lists (Box 54)
    - CSP Reports, Y-75-0218-C (Box 54)
    - MXCC B. Sherwill, 3 folders> (Box 54)
    - Middlesex Master File (Box 55)
    - MXCC equipment lists and costs (Box 55)
    - State Leasing Commission Report (Box 56)
    - Work records, Labor Dept. (Box 56)
    - Equipment lists (Box 56)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 56)
    - J. Marsella file (Box 56)
    - G. McCann file (Box 56)
    - E. Roscoe file (Box 56)
    - K. Summeror file (Box 56)
    - R. Biggs file (Box 56)
    - R. Hinze file (Box 56)
    - E. DeMatteo file (Box 56)
    - M. Tulin file (Box 56)
    - W. Mack file (Box 56)
    - P. Manaford file (Box 56)
    - MXCC equipment purchases (Box 56)
    - Allan Schaefer transcript (Box 56)
    - Bradley Biggs, John Marsella, Chet Zaneiwiski tapes (Box 56)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 57)
    - Rodger Ladd (Box 57)
    - Homicki (Box 57)
    - Art Banks (Box 57)
    - Henry Margolis (Box 57)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 58)
    - Brian Gaffney (Box 58)
    - T. DeLorenzo (Box 58)
    - Neckerman (Box 58)
    - R. Suisman (Box 58)
    - Henry Armstrong (Box 58)
    - Robert Drunchak (Box 58)
    - Ray Johns (Box 58)
    - M. Chambrello (Box 58)
    - Freedman (Box 58)
    - Roger Hinze (Box 58)
    - Newton (Box 58)
    - Donald Kerr (Box 58)
    - Roscoe (Box 58)
    - Audio tapes of State Police interviews (Box 59)
    - Thomas O'Marra (Box 59)
    - Stanley Page (Box 59)
    - Steward Smith (Box 59)
  - Nile Street Hospital file, 1945; 1987-018; .25 cubic feet
    - Report of Commission of State Police as Fire Marshal to State's Attorney for Hartford County concerning the fire in Hartford on December 24, 1945 at the Niles St. Hospital at 60 Niles Street, 2 copies (Box 60)
  - Taborsky and Colombe murder case (Mad Dog killers), 1956-1957; 1987-018; 1 cubic foot
    - Officer's Reports - Studebaker (Box 68)
    - Possessed Property Reports (Box 68)
    - Indexed Lists (Box 68)
    - Colombe's Statement (Box 68)
    - Taborsky's Statement (Box 68)
    - Officer Reports (Box 68)
    - Studebaker, 1950 and 1951 (Box 68)
    - Mrs. Colombe and daughter statements, bench warrants (Box 68)
    - Car Registration (Box 69)
    - Taborsky, Joseph et al - Bench Warrant (Box 69)
    - S-152M (Box 69)
    - S-33 (Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous investigation files, 1956-1957; 1987-018; 2 cubic feet
    - Bishop, S-152 (Box 70)
    - S-195M, Armed Robbery, Hartford, Leone's Taylor Shop (Box 70)
    - Statements (Box 70)
    - Letter File, A-B (Box 70)
    - Letter File, C-P (Box 71)
    - Letter File, R-Z (Box 72)
    - S-192M, Murder, Hartford, Rosenthal (Box 72)
    - IM-639, Double Murder, North Haven, Lungren (Box 72)
    - IM-639, Double Murder, North Haven, Lungren (Box 72)
    - IMP Runuffs-Automobiles (Box 73)
  - Charles Lindbergh Jr. kidnapping case, 1932; 1987-025; .25 cubic feet
    - Telegrams (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Telegrams and Wanted Poster (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Case Reports (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
    - List of currency numbers used to pay ransom (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hartford Circus Fire, 1941-1998; 4.5 cubic feet
    Hartford Circus Fire files are UNRESTRICTED
    - 1987-094, 4.25 cubic feet
      - Inquiries from the Press, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Certificates of Death, 1944; photostats (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Original Complaint, 1944; photocopy (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Circus Program and History of Circus, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Bleacher Occupant Lists, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Hartford Police Assignments, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Hartford Detective Statements, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Hartford Fire Department – Daily House Record, 1944 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Fire Department Personnel, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Birth Record, Edward Parsons Cook, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Circus Employee Statements, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Hartford Police Statements, A-F, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Hartford Police Statements, G-W, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Casualty Lists, 1944, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
      - Side-Wall Witnesses, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Missing Person Information, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)